I'm here !
Let's go.
I'm not going to die
Let's go, Redfish
And train and train some more
I'm gonna get even stronger
And faster
Yuno won't win
I'm gonna feed him to the finish line
And when I'm the wizard king
I'll come back for you, Sister Lily
So
Will you please marry me?
That Oscar's just full of surprises
The boy who barely got a grimoire is a regular magic night success story.
I'm glad to hear he's doing well.
They've both come so far in their young lives.
Abandoned on the doorstep when they were only babies.
And now look at them.
With the money they've sent home every month,
we fixed up the church and laid in enough pot potatoes
to keep everybody's stomachs full this winter.
Here is this.
Perfect, thanks.
Here you go.
Why don't you keep it?
Are you sure?
In this world, magic is everything.
So what could ever become of a boy who has none?
Now, never once has anyone from this region distinguished him or herself
by becoming a magic knight, much less the wizard king.
I pray that one among you will have what it takes
to become the most powerful mage in the land.
And now, to accept your grimoires.
Finally, my very own grimoire.
You know, was given the legendary four-leaf clover grimoire.
I will become the wizard king.
But, as for the magic-less Asta...
Hey, uh...
Is my grimoire running late or something?
Now, time for a hearty swig of magic-boosting mogul leaf juice.
Bottoms up!
Ah!
Oh, wow.
You're kidding.
That's actually kind of awesome.
What?
You don't have any magic!
How could you get a grimoire and that sword?
What kind of freak of nature are you?
Ah!
Yeah!
You took my spell and turned it into your magic power?
Even without traditional magic power,
I will be the wizard king!
My magic is never giving up!
Ah!
Well, what do you think?
My very own grimoire!
I don't know how it happened, but I got one!
Sounds like he's holding his own.
Juno, Asta, my boys!
You're the bride of the village!
Thank you, father.
The first time I saw Asta was on the day of the Magic Night's entrance exam.
Even then, there isn't any. He's sparkled.
Ha ha ha! One of us is gonna be the Wizard King!
This is where our legend begins! Right, you know?
I've been training for this the last six months!
Wait, will you see what I can do?
Why are they trying to kill me?!
What the hell?
Poor schmuck. Not the nicest welcome to the big city.
Get the hell away from me!
One of them. A real Magic Knight squad captain.
On to the next test. The final and most difficult. A display of combat skill.
As Knight's battle is our business, we want to see everything you're capable of!
The best way to show off now is to pair off with someone strong!
Ha ha! What do you say you and I pair up?
Do you really mean it, Seke? You're willing to take on a charity case like me?
We're both working for the same goal. So we'll have a fair fight, but nobody pulls any punches, okay?
No! Begin!
No pulling punches, remember?
Let's do this, Asta! Ha ha!
Bronze Creation Magic! Seke Magnum Cannonball!
Come on, don't get shy on me now!
Ha ha!
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Unlike you, Seke, I'm not joining the Magic Knights just so I can slack off and have a little fun!
I've got a much bigger goal! I'm gonna be the Wizard King!
So cool...
It's like magic is coming off him in waves!
This is it! The power of a Magic Knight captain!
What you said before? That you took the exam because you want to become the Wizard King?
And now, standing here magicless and pathetic, can you really say you have what it takes?
That you're strong enough to be the Wizard King?
Yeah, fine. So maybe I won't get to join a Magic Knight squad today.
But no matter what anyone says, and no matter how many times I might stumble, I won't give up! I will become the Wizard King!
Wizard King!
You know, kid, I like you! Come join our crew!
What?
Quit gaping like a fish! I'm saying I'll let you into the Black Bulls!
I wasn't the only one who saw the bright glow of Asta's inner light. The captain did, too. And that's the story about Asta's inner light.
And that's the story of how Asta came to join the Black Bulls family.
And let's not forget Asta's childhood friend. He was the only one who saw the bright glow of Asta's inner light. The captain did, too.
And that's the story of how Asta came to join the Black Bulls family. Let's not forget Asta's childhood friend, Yuno.
Do we have any hands?
No way? All of them? Impossible!
Has that ever happened?
I guess it's not just royalty and nobles who can get into the Golden Dawn.
Whoa! They all want him? Way to show him, Yuno!
I have to choose the squad that offers me the best path to becoming the Wizard King. It would be an honor to join the Golden Dawn.
What?
Asta and I are basically brothers now. So any childhood friend of his is a childhood friend of mine. In other words, Yuno and I are best friends.
Hmm.
Now then, time for today's entry in my observation diary.
Today, my dearish friend Asta worked his very hardest, just like he does at the time.
What?
Oh!
No! My heart belongs to Sister Lily, and I won't betray her for anybody!
Next!
Sit, Beastie!
There. Good boy. I think you've earned a treat.
What are you doing, you slobbery mutt? Let me go! I'm not your dinner!
It's so hot! I mean, maybe it is for a normal person, but this heat should be nothing to a black ball.
What's wrong? Do you want to get out already?
No, of course not! I can stay in! I'm not done yet!
Honestly, does he have a death wish? You're with me on this one, right, Nero? He's just so... so reckless.
And he's been that way since our very first mission. That ridiculous boar hunt.
We barely made it to Saucy Village when we were accosted by a band of thugs.
Hey, Asta!
Sir!
Kill them.
Think again!
Sure!
Do you imagine you can still protect your herd of beasts like this?
Cluster!
Too late.
You stand no chance of prevailing against me.
Why not accept that and give up?
If I gave up now, then who would protect them?
I realized something.
Sooner or later, I'm going to be the Wizard King.
But it's not just about keeping a promise.
It's about keeping people safe!
Wizard King might fight!
What does he think would have happened if I hadn't been there?
Well, I did mentally cheer for him, but still...
It's not like that means anything.
Not really.
This has to stop!
It's not like that!
I mean, me and that idiot commoner?
There's no way!
I'm royalty!
And he's basically a lunatic.
Like back in the dungeon.
Your new opponent!
He's right here!
What for me?
Be gone, boy!
Why are you just sitting there, Insect?
You're awake!
Now get moving.
And don't you dare give up until you beat him.
Understand?
Yeah.
I'll bring this guy down, and I'll get one or two hits in for you while I'm at it.
Give up.
You can't win.
I live to destroy the weak.
Well, you're not going to destroy me!
I may not have any magic power, but what I do have are my friends!
I don't really know how, but I did it.
I'm dead.
What's happening?
Let's die!
Even if he was fine in the end.
Might be dead if it weren't for you.
Thanks a lot.
I'm so very sorry!
You were really great back there.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
Sorry I kind of ruined the mixer for you.
You didn't, though.
Hey, Asta?
Do you have anyone who's special to you?
Yes!
I've got my heart set on someone!
Someone's special, huh?
Someone he's got his heart set on.
If he cares so much, he shouldn't make me worry.
Who's making you worry?
How long have you been there anyway?
It isn't nice to sneak up on people!
Not long.
I just got back from an epic training session.
What are you up to in here?
We've been given a mission of grave importance.
Right, we're ready.
You know, perhaps it would be best if you stayed behind.
If your injuries aren't healed...
I'll be fine.
It's so sweet of you to put Yuno's health first like that.
I am not sweet.
Bringing along an injured man would slow us down, that's all.
My concern is for the mission, not Yuno's health.
Let's go.
You're not riding?
Well, uh...
It's just more of a broom sort of day.
You know?
Don't be shy.
It doesn't use too much magic power if that's what you're worried about.
Oh, I'm not being shy.
And I'm definitely not thinking about how embarrassing it would be if my friend saw me riding in that.
Yeah.
Now see here!
Are you two making fun of my chariot?
Of course not.
Hey!
Come back!
You can't take off on your own like that!
Well, I'll just be on my way too then!
I can't waste any time resting.
I need to get stronger.
Much stronger.
You showed me it was possible.
Gave me hope.
That even though we're poor orphans,
commoners,
we can still make something of ourselves in this world.
And to prove that,
to make Sister Lily and everybody else happy.
We'll fight to see who will be the Wizard King!
Whatever it takes!
Thanks so much for watching.
Thanks for being here!
Thank you.
Alright!
Let's see if I play as well as I fight!
Thank you.